{
    "id": "6ad8d08034fa4800a2d265ce04d4b04e",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………… sleep well yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't",
                "couldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a073009423894fcdbcc9f37664a5267f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has just left",
                "had just left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5fe4e94da12d49ff9eaa331db9f59afa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. college last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "was leaving",
                "have left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7cbbc87f7f1349469f21ecf33728c8bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The light …………………. out while I was reading.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "goes",
                "go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "865eb4e9bf074a92831a20c82515f93f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The light always …………………. out when I am about to study.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "goes",
                "has gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "afce92ce67254514a1683cf46eaa8b05"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ..................... the piano when I met her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was playing",
                "played",
                "has played"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "558216240a7a46689aded06fc93fa285"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever ………………… to Singapore?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "be",
                "being"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cd0675b11add47cc9c0f6f67be2de01a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Every morning, he ....................... for a walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "goes",
                "go",
                "has gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "371df092011e4edba029e90d1a741494"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team …………………. the West Indies yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "defeated",
                "was defeated",
                "had defeated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c2593a55ee2d4db79e343322d44c0a5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. several books.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has written",
                "had written",
                "wrote"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24b0d9f9e2ae4e8091f9217213f07f28"
        }
    ]
}